Guide to the Pennsylvania Economy League Records, 1925-1985 AIS.1978.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- School District Reports, 1939-1987; I.
  - Central Greene, "Student Transportation Study Central Greene School District", October, 1971
  - Charleroi, "A Study of the Charleroi Area Joint School District", December, 1960 (Box 3)
  - Cheswick, "A General Guide to the Fiscal Effects of School Reorganization in Allegheny County Administrative Unit #9 (Cheswick, Borough, Harman Township, Springdale Borough, Springdale Township)", July, 1964
  - Clairton, "Administrative and Fiscal Survey of the School District City of Clairton", December, 1951
  - Clairton, "A Study of the School Building Requirements Elementry and Secondary", August, 1952
  - Clairton (Washington County), "The Financial Impact of an Eight District Merger in Administrative Unit XI", April, 1961
  - Clarks, "Report on the Present and Future School Plant Requirements Clarks Summit-Abington Joint School Board", January, 1953
  - Coatesville, "A Study of the School Plant Faciliteis in the Coatesville Area of Chester County, Pennsylvania", January, 1950
  - Coatesville, "The Effects of Merger and Financial Tends in the Years 1963-1968"
  - Conestoga (Lancaster County), "A Community School Plan: A Supplement to a Study of the School Plant Facilities of the Millersville Area of Lancaster County", January, 1950
  - Conestoga (Lancaster County), "A Study of the School Plant Facilities of the Millersvlle Area of Lancaster County: Six School Districts Study their Plant Needs on a Long-Range Basis", January, 1950
  - Connellsville, "A Study of the Connellsville City School District Fayette County, Pennsylvania and the School Districts in the Connellsville Area", November, 1950
  - Connellsville, "Connellsville Joint School District Providing Water Facilites for the Porposed Senior High School", July, 1954
  - Connellsville, "Connellsville Joint School System Analsis of Jointure Expenses and Jointure Expense Allocation of Proposed Complete Jointure", April, 1958
  - Connellsville, "Connellsville Area School District Actual and Projected Enrollments 1976-77 to 1986-87", November, 1981
  - Conyngham, "Report on Conyngham Township School District Columbia County, PA", August, 1950
  - Coolspring, "A Study of Five School Districts (Coolspring, E Lackawannock, Findley, Jefferson, & Mercer) with a Suggested Budget for Joint Operation", April, 1948
  - Coraopolis, "Analysis of the 1947-48 Budget of the Coraopolis Borough School District with Projections for he 1948-49 Budget Requirements", November, 1947
  - Coraopolis, "A General Guide to the Fiscal Effects of School Reorganization in Allegheny County Administrative Unit #35 (Coraopolis Borough, Moon Union, Neville Township)", May, 1964
  - Cumberland, "A Community Studies Its Schools", October, 1948
  - Cumberland, "A School Building and Financial Survey of Cumberland Township School District", March, 1950
  - Cumberland, "Memorandum Report on Cumberland Township School Finances", April, 1959
  - Cumberland, "Administrative Organization, Practices, and Procedures in Cumberland Township School District", October, 1959
  - Dauphin County, "Toward Better Schools through Cooperation: A Study of Nine Contiguous School Districts made at the Request of the Superintendent of Schools of Dauphine County, Pennsylvania", March, 1948
  - Dauphin County, "The Schools of Northern Dauphin County", June, 1948
  - Dauphine County, "Another Community Studies its Schools", May, 1949
  - Deer Lakes, "A Long Range Development Program Deer Lake School District Dreighton, Pennsylvania", June, 1969
  - Delaware County, "A School Plant Program for Eigheen School Districts of Delaware and Chester County, Pennsylvania", 1952
  - Delaware County, "A Preliminary Report on High School Needs", 1954
  - Derry, "Survey of the Derry Township School Disrict Westomoreland County", April, 1952
  - Derry, "Derry Area School District Long Range Development Program Two-Year Revision Community Growth and Population Trends", January, 1972
  - Derry, "Philosophy of a School Finance Projection Procedural Checklist", February, 1973
  - Derry, "A Fiscal Survey of the Long Range Developmenal Program for the Derry Area School District", March, 1973
  - Derry, "Derry Area School District Enrollment and Financial Projection 1979-80 to 1983-84", May, 1979
  - Derry, "Derry Area School District Actual and Projected Enrollmetns 1976-77 to 1986-87", November, 1981
  - Dickson City, "Analysis Fanancial Condition and Adminisrative Organization of Dickson City School", June, 1958
  - Donora, "Survey of the School District of the Borough of Donora Washington County", November, 1946
  - Donora, "A Review of the 1947-48 Tentative Budget of the Donora Borough School District", May, 1947
  - Donora, "A Review of the 1948-49 Revenue and Expenditure Estimates of the Borough of Donora School District (Washington County)", April, 1948
  - Donora, "Report to the Donora Borough School District on the Problem of Administering and Collecting the Earned Income and Wage Tax", 1955
  - Donora, "Comments on the Proposed Budget for the School Year 1957-58 of the Donora Borough School District"
  - Donora, "A Study of the Donora Borough School District Washington County", 1959
  - Donora, "A Budgetary Review of the Donora School District 157-58 to 1963-64", June, 1963
  - Dravosburg, "Proposed Reorganization of Administrative Units Involving the School Districts of Dravosburg, Duquesne, and West Mifflin", December, 1956
  - DuBois, "A Study of the City of Dubois School District Clearfield County, Pennsylvania", April,1949
  - Dunbar, "A School Study: Organization, School Plant Facilities and Finances", August, 1947
  - Dunkard, "A Study of the Secondary School Building Problem Southeastern Greene Joint School District Greene County", July, 1952
  - Dunkard, "Local per Pupil Costs of Education Dunkard Township School District – Green County", October, 1952
  - Dunkard, "A General Guide to the Fiscal Effects of School Reorganization in Green County Administrative Unit #63-5", Unkown
  - Duquesne, "Preparation of the 1947-48 Budget Duquesne School District", Apirl, 1947
  - East Deer, "An Analysis of Trends in Public School Enrollments and Finances in the East Deer-Frazer and West Deer School Districts", October, 1958 (Box 4)
  - East Deer, "A Survey Report On Fiscal Problems Confronting the East Deer-Frazier Union School District", October, 1963
  - East Huntington, "Financial Data East Huntington Township School Districts", February, 1958
  - East Washington, "A Report on East Washington School Operations", May, 1952
  - East Washington, "A Study of the East Washington Borough School District Washington County", November, 1956
  - Elizabeth, "A Study of the Present School Plant Immediate Needs and Future Considerations Financial Analysis", August, 1946
  - Ellwood City, "A Review and Forecast of School Fiscal Operations in the Ellwood City Area", March, 1964
  - Etna, "The Public School Situation in the Etna, Millvale, and Shaler School Districts", June, 1958
  - Farrell, "A Survey to Determine the Advisability of Establishing a Larger Administrative Unit Mercer County", March, 1957
  - Farrell, "A Survey to Determine the Advisability of Establishing a Larger Administrative Unit - Revised Edition Mercer County", October, 1957
  - Farrell, "A Financial and Administrative Study of the Farrell School District Mercer County", May, 1958
  - Farrell, "Procedures for the Assessment and Collection of Per Capita Tax", July, 1959
  - Farrell, "Farrell Area School District Office Procedures", October, 1960
  - Farrell, "An Analysis of the Farrell Area School District Fiscal Program", March, 1967
  - Farrell, "Proposed Bookkeeping and Accounting System for Federal Funds", September, 1968
  - Farrell, "An Analysis of Financing the New High School Its Impact on the 1968-69 General Fund Budget", February, 1968
  - Farrell, "Grwoing Smaller: A Problem for the Farrell Area School Distict as Enrollments Continue to Decline", March, 1979
  - Farrell City, "Financial Operations of the City of Farrell School District 1934-35 – 1946-47", June, 1948
  - Farrell City, "An Analysis of the 1948-49 Tentative Budget for the City of Farrell School District", June, 1948
  - Farrell City, "A Study of the School District of the City of Farrell, Pennsylvania", June, 1950
  - Fayette County Schools, "Standard Accounting Forms and Procedures for School Districts and Joint School Systems", June, 1958
  - Fayette County Schools, "Population and Enrollment in Administrative Districts II: Townships of Washington, Perry, Jefferson, Lower Tyrone, Boroughs Bell Vernon, Fayetter City, Newell, Perryopolis", April, 1962
  - Fayette County Schools, "Population and Enrollment in Administrative Districts I: Townships Georges, German, Nicholson, Springhill, Boroughs Georges, Masontown, Point Marion, Smithfield", July, 1962
  - Fayette County Schools, "Indebtedness and Borrowing Capacity Fayette County Municipalities and School Districts", September, 1962
  - Fayette County Schools, "Population and Enrollment in Administrative District IV: Townships Bullskin, Connellsville, Saltlick, Springfield, Borough Dawson, Dunbar, South Connellsville, Vanderbilt, and Connellsville City", April, 1963
  - Fayette County Schools, "Population and Enrollment in Administrative District V: North and South Union Township", February, 1964
  - Fayette County Schools, "Population and Enrollment in Administrative District VI: Township Franklin, Menallen, Marclay, Wharton Union, New Salem Independent, Ohiopylie-Stewart Joint, Uniontown City", February, 1964
  - Fayette County Schools, "Population and Enrollment in Administrative District III: Township Luzerne, Redstone, Brownsville, Boroughs Brownsville, West Brownsville", June, 1964
  - Fayette County Schools, "A General Guide to the Fiscal Effects of School Reorganization in Fayette County", August, 1964
  - Ford City (Armstrong County), "Planning for Better Education: A Jointure Study Including the School Districts of Armstrong County", January, 1952
  - Ford City, "Ford City Union School District a Report on Its Present School Plan", May, 1956
  - Fox Chapel, "Improved Collection of Earned Income Tax in the Fox Chapel Area School District", November, 1961
  - Franklin, "A Survey of the Franklin Township School District Westmoreland County", July, 1948
  - Franklin, "Planning for Adequate Educational Facilities in the Franklin Area Joint School System", April, 1957
  - Franklin, "Proposed Organizational Plan and Positions for the Business Office of the Merged School District of Franklin, Perry, Washington, Wayne, and Whiteley Townships and Waynesburg Borough", June, 1962
  - Franklin, "A Survey of the Area Population and Pupil Enrollments of the Franklin Regional School District", November, 1971
  - Franklin, "Franklin Regional School District Actual and Projected Enrollments 1976-77 to 1986-87", November, 1981
  - Franklin, "Franklin Regional School District Actual and Projected Enrollments 1978-79 to 1988-89", March, 1984
  - Frazier, "A Long-Range Developmental Program for Frazier School District, Fayette County, Part IV Finances and Obligations", September, 1967
  - Gateway, "Gateway School District Actual and Projected Enrollments 1976-77 to 1986-87", November, 1981
  - German, "German Township School District Fiscal Review and Examination of 1948-49 Tentative Budget", June, 1948
  - Glenolden, "A United Effort on a Common Problem: The School Boards of Glenolden and Norwood Jointly Analyze their Future School Building Needs", February, 1954
  - Greene County, "A Report on Greene County School Districts and The Financial Impact of A 35 Percent Ratio for Tax Purposes on these Districts", October, 1960
  - Greene County, "A Program of Special Education for Greene County", April, 1961
  - Greensburg, "Salient Financial Facts of the Greensburg School District 1943-44 – 1954-55", May, 1954
  - Greensburg, "Greensburg School District 1957-58 Tentative Budget", May, 1957
  - Greensburg, "Opportunities for Cooperation", January, 1967
  - Greensburg, "A Fiscal Survey of the Long Range Development Program for the Greensburg Salem School District", June, 1971
  - Greenville, "Financial Analysis of Greenville Borough School District 1939-40 – 1948-50 (Includes Tentative 1949-1950 Budget)", April, 1949
  - Greenville, "A Reorganization Study Including Greenville Borough, Hempfield, West Salem, Sugar Grove Townships School District", June, 1951
  - Greenville, "A Summary of the Immediate & Long-Range Housing Requirements for the Greenville Area Joint School District", April, 1953
  - Greenville, "A Report on School Building Needs and School Building Finances of the Greenville Area Joint School District and Member Districts Thereof", May, 1956
  - Greenville, "A Union School District", August, 1958
  - Grove City, "The Advantages and Disadvantages of Operating the Grove City Consolidated Schools as a Union School District", March, 1959
  - Grove City, "A Study of Pupils, Finances, and Stffing in the Grove City Area School District", January, 1978
  - Harmony, "A Report to the School Districts of Harmony Borough, Lancaster Township Zelienhope Borough Relative to School Jointure Possibilities", April, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Hazelton, "School Plant Facilities Hazleton City School District", July, 1951
  - Hazelton, "Hazleton City School District Tentative Budget 1958-59", May, 1958
  - Hempfield, "A Survey of the Hempfield Township School District Westmoreland County", August, 1948
  - Hempfield, "The Hempfield Joint School System", April, 1958
  - Hickory, "Transportation Alternatives in the Hickory Township School District", June, 1975
  - Hermitage, "Hermitage School District Actual and Projected Enrollments 1976-77 to 1986-87", 1987
  - Hollidaysburg, "Multiperil Insurance Specifications Hollidaysburg Area School District", May, 1966
  - Hollidaysburg, "Multiperil Insurance Specifications Automobile Liability and Physical Damage Specifications", April, 1969
  - Hollidaysburg, "Hollidaysburg Area School District Pupil Enrollment Projection 174-75 – 1978-79", 1979
  - Hollidaysburg, "Hollidaysburg Area School District Actual and Projected Enrollments 1976-77 to 1986-87", November, 1981
  - Hollidaysburg, "Hollidaysburg Area School District Actual and Projected Enrollments 1979-80 to 1989-90", January, 1985
  - Hopewell, "A Study of Projected Growth, Construction Needs and Financial Impact: Part I Projected Enrollment and Construction Needs", February, 1958
  - Hopewell, "A Study of Projected Growth, Construction Needs and Financial Impact: Part II Financing the Program", April, 1959
  - Jeannette City, "A Survey of the Operations of the Jeannette School District", April, 1959
  - Jeannette City, "The League Reviews the 1970-71 Preliminary Budget of the Jeannette City School District", June, 1970
  - Jeannette City, "A Fiscal Analysis and Projection of the Jeannette City School District 1959-60 through 1979-80", October, 1970
  - Jefferson, "Financial Analysis and Building Program Projections to 1970", July, 1946
  - Jefferson, "A General Guide to the Fiscal Effects of School Reorganizaiton in Green County Administrative Unit #63-3", September, 1964
  - Johnstown, "Enrollment Trends and Forecast Greater Johnstown School Districts 1970-71 and 1982-1983", December, 1977
  - Keystone, "Keystone Oaks School District Actual and Projected Enrollments 1976-77 to 1986-87", October, 1981
  - Kittanning, "A Study of the Kittanning Area Secondary School System Armstrong County: Relative to the Building of One New Secondary Building", January, 1953
  - Kittanning, "Survey of the Accounting and Bookkeeping Systems of the Kittanning Union School District and the Kittanning Area Secondary School System", September, 1954
  - Kittanning, "A Report on the Tax Impact if a Union School Distric were Formed Consisting of Kitanning Union, East Franklin, North Buffalo, Rayburn, Valley Township District", June, 1959
  - Kiski (Armstrong County), "Financial Trends and Outlook of the Kiski Area Joint School District", January, 1962
  - Kiskiminetas, "The League Studies the Financial Impact of School Distric Reorganization in the Boroughs of Apollo, North Apollo, and Kiskiminetas Township in Armstrong County, and Jacksonville Borough, Young Township, and West Labanon Independent District in Indiana Conty", February, 1964
  - Lakeview, "Shall The Lakeview Joint Schools Become a Union School District?", April, 1959
  - Lakeview (Mercer County), "Shall the Lakeview Joint Schools Become a Union School District? Revision of Local Tax Information", February, 1961
  - Lakeview, "Review of Earned Income Tax Collection Procedures in the Lakeview Area School District", August, 1978
  - Lakeview, "Lakeview School District Actual and Projected Enrollments 1976-77 to 1986-87", October, 1981
  - Lancaster City, "A Survey of the School District of the City of Lancaster, Pennsylvania", 1953
  - Lansdale (Montgomery County), "A Program for Improvement of School Plant Facilities in the Lansdale Area of Montgomery County, Pennsylvania: Eight School Districts Study Their Plant Needs on a Long-Range Basis", July, 1950
  - Latrobe, "Memorandum on the Preliminary 1949-50 Budget Latrobe School District", April, 1949
  - Latrobe, "A Survey of the Latrobe Borough School District", June, 1949
  - Latrobe, "Reorganization a Report to the School Districts of Latrobe Borough, Unity Township, Youngstown Borough", May, 1956
  - Latrobe, "A Merged School District for the Greater Latrobe Area: Latrobe Borough, Unity Township, Youngstown Borough", April, 1962
  - Latrobe, "Survey and Evaluation Greater Latrobe School District", May, 1966
  - Laurel Valley (Westmoreland County), "Memorandum on Laurel Valley Joint School District", May, 1953
  - Leechburg, "A Survey of the School Districts In the Leechburg Area Relative to the Desirability of Combining All or Part of the Following Districts", July, 1953
  - Leechburgh, "Method of Computing and Administering a Uniform Tax Levy on School Districts Crossing County Lines, November, 1971
  - Leechburg, "Leechburg Area School District Actual and Projected Enrollments 1977-78 to 1987-88", September, 1982
  - Ligonier, "School Plant and Financial Survey Ligonier Township School District Westmoreland County", May, 1950
  - Ligonier Valley, "School Financial Problems in the Ligonier Valley", November, 1957
  - Ligonier Valley, "Survey of the Ligonier Valley School District", April, 1967
  - Ligonier Valley, "Ligonier Valley School District: Enrollment Trends and the Advisability of Closing the John Ramsey Elementary Building", August, 1980
  - Luzerne, "A Study of the Luzerne Township School District Fayette County", May, 1949
  - Luzerne County, "A Report on Area Planning for Education in Lower Luzerne County", May, 1957
  - Malvern (Chester County), "Improving Educational Opportunities: Along the Main Line Five School Districts Study their Schools Plant Needs on a Long-Range Basis", April, 1951
  - Manheim, "Analysis of Manheim Township School District Pupil Transpiration Costs 1945-46", February, 1945
  - Masontown (Southwestern Fayette County), "School Plant Survey Southwestern Fayette County Including: Masontown Borough, Nicholson Township, Point Marion Borough, Smithfield Borough, Springhill Township School District", July, 1950
  - Mars (Butler County), "Mars Area School District Business Office Analysis", February, 1974
  - Mars (Butler County), "Mars Area School District Transportation", March, 1974
  - Mars (Butler County), "Mars Area School District Actual and Projected Enrollments 1976-77 to 1986-87"
  - Mauch Chunk, "Report on Building & Personnel Utilization Mauch Chunk Township School District", April, 1955
  - Mauch Chunk, "Administrative Review of the Mauch Chunk Township School District", March, 1959
  - McKeesport, "A Study of the School District of the City of McKeesport, Pennsylvania", February, 1950 (Box 6)
  - McKeesport, "A General Guide to the Fiscal Effects of School District Reorganization in McKeesport Area", May, 1964
  - Mercer, "Mercer Joint Consolidated Schools Classroom Needs", December, 1959
  - Mercer, "Mercer County, Institution District: $1,700,000 Proposed Bond Issue Financial Study", March, 1959
  - Mercer, "Secretarial/Clerical Positions in Selected School Districts: Comparative Data", January, 1979
  - Midland (Beaver County), "Midland Borough School District a Financial Picture", August, 1960
  - Midland, "A Comprehensive Fiscal Study of the Midland Borough School District", April, 1976
  - Middleton (Central Delaware), "A Brief Report on a School Site Evaluation for the Central Delaware County Joint School Board", 1953
  - Monaca, "Monaca School District Actual and Projected Enrollment 1977-78 to 1987-88", November, 1982
  - Monessen City, "A Survey of the Monessen City School District Westmoreland County: Made at the Request of the Monessen Board of Education", February, 1950
  - Monessen City, "The Monessen School District a Survey of School Plant Facilities", May, 1965
  - Moniteau, "Multiperial Insurance Specificaitons for Moniteau School District", January, 1971
  - Monogahela, "A Report on the Financial Aspects of Merging School Districts in the Donora-Monogahela Area School District", March, 1963
  - Monogahela, "A Report on the Financial Aspects of Merging School Districts in the Donora-Monogahela Area School District Vol. II Exhibits", March, 1963
  - Montgomery County, "A Report Covering New Amendments to the Authorities Act and the Reorganization of School Districts", April, 1952
  - Montgomery County, "The Reorganization of School Districts in Montgomery County", May, 1953
  - Montgomery County, "12 Districts get Together in Seeking a Solution to School Problems", February, 1954
  - Montgomery County, "Financing Education, & Cost In Montgomery County", April, 1954
  - Montour, "Montour School District Actual and Projected Enrollments 1976-77 to 1986-87", December, 1981
  - Moon, "Moon Township School District, Allegheny County: A Proposed Reorganized Administrative Unit", May, 1952
  - Morgan, "Morgan Township School District Financial Survey", May, 1962
  - Mount Pleasant, "The Relation of Tuition Pupils to the Mount Pleasant Borough School District", May, 1954
  - Mount Pleasant, "Selected School District Data: Tabulated for the Mount Pleasant Borough School District", November, 1960
  - Mount Pleasant, "Mount Pleasant Area School District Actual and Projected Enrollment 1976-77 to 1986-87"
  - Mt. Carmel, "A Study of a Proposed Combined School System for the Districts of Mt. Caramel Borough and Mt. Carmel Township", September, 1951
  - Mt. Lebanon, "A Study of the Mt. Lebanon School District Allegheny County", September, 1948
  - Munhall, "A Study of the Munhall Borough School District, Allegheny County Pennsylvania", October, 1949
  - Nanticoke, "Report on Administration & Organization Nanticoke City Schools", April, 1954
  - Neshaminy, "A Study of the School Plant Facilities of he Neshaminy Area of Bucks County: Six School Districts Study Their School Plant Needs on a Long-Range Basis", November, 1949
  - Nether Providence, "Report to Board of Directors of the School District of Nether Providence Township Concerning Pupil Transporation", May, 1941
  - Neville Island, "Neville Island School District Review of the 1948-49 Proposed Budget", May, 1948
  - New Brighton, "School Merger for the New Brighton Area: Daugherty TWP", June, 1955
  - New Brighton, "A Union School District for New Brighton Area Joint Schools: New Brighton, Pulaski, Daugherty Joint School District", August, 1960
  - New Brighton, "New Brighton Area School District Building Program Criteria for Making Decisions", December, 1964
  - New Kensington, "A Study of the School District of the City of New Kensington", December, 1950